<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Public Space as a Catalyst for Change in Informal Settlements</title>
    <description>Website exploring the importance of public space in informal settlements, possible design solutions, tools, strategies, etc.
</description>
    <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 11:00:35 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 11:00:35 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Informality: a global overview</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;an-urban-world&quot;&gt;An Urban World.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As predicted by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mike_Davis_(scholar)&quot;&gt;Mike Davis&lt;/a&gt; in his famous book &lt;em&gt;Planet of Slums&lt;/em&gt; in 2007 for the first time the urban population has outnumbered the rural one. &lt;a href=&quot;https://data.worldbank.org/indicator/sp.urb.totl.in.zs?end=2018&amp;amp;start=1960&amp;amp;view=chart&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt; In this process of accelerated urbanization, today, more than 55% of the world’s population lives in an urban area or city, with that figure set to rise to 68% over the coming decades (According to the “&lt;a href=&quot;https://population.un.org/wpp/&quot;&gt;Population Division&lt;/a&gt;” report from the UN’s Department of Economic and Social Affairs).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Urban-Population-Growth-1950-to-2050.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Urban Population Growth 1950-2050&quot; title=&quot;Urban Population Growth 1950 to 2050&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Growth in urban population is not equally distributed, the scale and velocity of urbanization in developing countries is unprecedented and astonishing if compared with any other period of human history. The number of megacities has exploded in the last decades changing the world’s urban hierarchies and networks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However megacities are just one aspect of the urbanization of the world, small and medium size cities are also growing everywhere in the world and they are absorbing the vast majority of the new urban dwellers. In most cases new urban settlers come from poorer contexts and don’t have access to formal housing solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;informality&quot;&gt;Informality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of this 55% of world population -that roughly sums 4.2 Billion people- an estimated 25% of the world’s urban population lives in informal settlements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Share-of-urban-population-living-in-slums-GIF.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Share of urban population living in slums&quot; title=&quot;Share of urban population living in slums&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Urban-Slums-Population-GIF.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Urban Population living in slums&quot; title=&quot;Urban Population living in slums&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yet, due to the speed, scale, complexity, and singularity nature of informality, the discipline of design and planning still lacks the adequate knowledge and strategies to understand and address this global phenomenon adequately.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2020/05/19/a-planet-of-slums/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2020/05/19/a-planet-of-slums/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Informal settlements in Argentina</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;informal-settlements-in-argentina&quot;&gt;Informal Settlements in Argentina&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Argentina&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2020/05/15/informal-argentina/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2020/05/15/informal-argentina/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Public Space as a Catalyst for Change in Informal Settlements</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In this context, it is urgent for designers and planners to explore understudied topics beyond dwelling and infrastructure, such as public space, which may challenge the existing notions of informality. Interventions in communal areas are often downplayed, but they may be central in striving for equity and urban integration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a multidimensional aspect, public space is highly relevant when meeting the population’s needs, creating an equitable built environment, assessing decision-making processes, and enhancing community networks. Nonetheless, its significance and relevance in informal settlements are yet to be fully explored. For this research, public space interventions in the latter context are open-ended opportunities to compensate for individual shortages in the built environment by exploring frameworks for cross-scalar action, collective agency, emotional and cognitive development, environmental awareness, and other topics related both to individual and community welfare. It is a tangible area to strive for equity and inclusion, one that is loosely defined nowadays when referring to informal settlements and that could be an entry point for planners and designers to imagine new systems of integration in the short, medium, and long-term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This research was developed as a support material for a seminar at the GSD with the same title. During the course students had to think prospectively about the aforementioned scenarios, particularly working on innovative strategies in design and planning. They had to draw on several sources, including the &lt;a href=&quot;http://relevamiento.techo.org.ar/&quot;&gt;Argentinian nationally-produced database: “Registro Nacional de Barrios Populares” (RENABAP)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/ecosistemaurbano-corrientes.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The main public space in the Dr.Montaña settlement, in Corrientes, Argentina&quot; title=&quot;The main public space in the Dr.Montaña settlement, in Corrientes, Argentina&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RENABAP is a survey that accounts for more than 4,000 settlements across the country, ranging from extremely dense urban “villas” to low density peripheral “asentamientos”. The challenge will be to discern patterns across both the formal and informal city to provide frameworks for action that consider the newly-produced information, particularly through the lens of understanding and decreasing vulnerability with strategies surrounding public space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At large, the course has been organized following 6 topics, each of which has been framed and understood through the lenses of public space:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/07/25/Community&quot;&gt;Community and Social Development&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/07/26/Resources&quot;&gt;Resources and Waste&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/07/27/Education&quot;&gt;Education and Innovation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/07/28/Mobility&quot;&gt;Mobility and Accessibility&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/07/29/Infrastructure&quot;&gt;Infrastructure and Resilience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/2019/07/30/Implementation&quot;&gt;Implementation and Management&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2020/05/10/public-space/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2020/05/10/public-space/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Implementation and Management</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Can public space be the backbone to conceptualize sustainable processes that include and benefit communities in both their short-term deployment and long-term maintenance?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As previously stated, all planning and design interventions must envision systems and processes both for implementation and long-term sustainability of the actions, incorporating notions of social and environmental resilience. This includes establishing frameworks for bottom-up inclusion, incorporation of local perspectives, and contextualized solutions. Perhaps one of the most challenging topics, this area refers to how solutions are achieved and maintained, ratherly than merely what those interventions may look like. For this course, outcomes are as important as processes, framing public space as a key actor for such dynamics to unravel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possible topics to be addressed: sustainable implementation, collective management, collective ownership, long-term planning, participation strategies, incorporation of traditional knowledge and social practices, power dynamics, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/30/implementation/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/30/implementation/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mobility and Accessibility</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How can public space advocate for systems that strengthen informal settlements, particularly as they face the rising and disproportionate burdens of socio-environmental threats?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For underserved communities to flourish despite recurring socio-environmental disruptions and existing vulnerabilities, there ought to be frameworks in place to foster resilience. Either to prepare for the imminent effects of climate change or resist structural injustice, designers and planners should envision systems and spaces that promote flexibility, agency, and adaptability. Infrastructure is then how such frameworks are conceived, regardless of them being tangible or intangible. Public space may become a platform to advocate for the creation of systems that strengthen informal settlements, particularly as they face the disproportionate burdens of socio-environmental threats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possible topics to be addressed: equitable resilience, environmental justice, climate change, climate adaptation and mitigation, disaster response, hydrology, social infrastructure, self-sufficiency, economic resilience, migration and displacement, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/29/inrastructure/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/29/inrastructure/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mobility and Accessibility</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What can public space do to boost community assets and spawn integrative, complementary, or alternative transportation, service provision, and connectivity patterns?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fringe communities, many of which may be informal settlements in large urban settings, are often effectively disconnected from their formal counterparts. This signifies a momentous burden for those who commute on a daily basis, both as an economic disadvantage and a social detriment. Time consumed in daily transportation routes, for example, may disrupt interpersonal relationships, individual welfare, and collective capacity for engagement. On the other hand, lack of access to services and opportunities within the formal city, may also disproportionately impact residents from informal settlements. Different mobility patterns may then trickle down to several other layers, significantly impacting integration and development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possible topics to be addressed: connectivity, public transportation, alternative mobility means, universal accessibility, transit-oriented development, grid interconnections, healthcare, access to public services, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/28/mobility/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/28/mobility/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Education and Innovation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Can the implementation of innovative public space strategies and new technologies act as cascading examples for capacity building, community empowerment, and grassroots data generation?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interventions in the public realm have numerous advantages, one of which is undoubtedly to serve as examples of city making processes and catalyzers of new social dynamics. Understanding that every design and planning intervention is political by nature, there is significant room to explore how actions may serve multiple purposes, including awareness and capacity  building. Informal settlements are also places where great creativity and entrepreneurship arises, both of which are critical assets when putting forward sustainable urban models that may initiate grassroots action and rely on new technologies to advocate for development. Therefore, strategies for public space may also be framed as cutting-edge proposals both for educational, social, and technological advancement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possible topics to be addressed: Inclusive/grassroots mapping, Participatory Action Research, data co-creation, awareness through urban interventions, knowledge sharing, user-generated platforms, new technologies, smart cities, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/27/education/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/27/education/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Resources and Waste</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;What is the role of public space in managing the production and consumption of resources, as well as the disposal of residues within informal areas that often exist at the margins?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Underserved communities, such as informal settlements, often exist in places where natural resources are the scarcest, effectively setting them up for enhanced vulnerability in relationship to the formal city. Production, consumption, and disposal of goods and natural resources have great potential to be incorporated within systems to counter the prior scenario, namely within the realm of public space. Both for the present and future, ensuring access to resources in informal settlements is a complex issue for designers and planners to tackle, but it may also represent one of the most straightforward paths to begin breaching the inequality gap in cities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possible topics to be addressed: Access to potable water, food production/consumption, residues treatment, recycling of materials and resources, pollution, waste disposal services, local materials, sustainable energy, sanitation, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/26/resources/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/26/resources/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Community and Social Development</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How can public space address topics beyond the physical to nurture stronger communities that may generate microeconomic networks and develop collective agency?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Relationships are arguably a central topic when intervening in urban settings, and, as such, should be fully explored in the natural built, and social environment. This last aspect refers to an ample range of intangible ties and trends, which may substantially contribute both to individual and collective well-being. If unattended, however, it may also present significant challenges from the conception to the long-term sustainability of any proposal. It is of the utmost importance for designers and planners to engage with such complex issues, particularly as it refers to underserved communities. In other words, proposals should fully grasp relevant topics beyond the physical, helping generate stronger communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possible topics to be addressed: Identity, heritage, diversity, gender equality, economic development, demographic trends, formal vs. informal economies, community empowerment, bottom-up agency, frameworks for social integration, chronic violence, community outreach, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/25/community/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/25/community/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UN Habitat Standards for Adequate Living</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-definition-of-slum&quot;&gt;The definition of Slum&lt;/h2&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/21/adequate-living/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/07/21/adequate-living/</guid>
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Violence Prevention Through Urban Upgrading</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Violence0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Violence0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Violence1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Violence1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Violence/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Violence/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tracing Public Spaces</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Tracing0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tracing0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Tracing1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tracing1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Tracing/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Tracing/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tegucigalpa Revitalization</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Tegucigalpa0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tegucigalpa0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Tegucigalpa1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Tegucigalpa1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Tegucigalpa/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Tegucigalpa/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Parque Hídrico La Quebradora</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Quebradora0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Quebradora0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Quebradora1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Quebradora1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Quebradora/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Quebradora/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PiggyBack Yard</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/PiggyBack0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PiggyBack0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/PiggyBack1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;PiggyBack1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/PiggyBack/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/PiggyBack/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Night-Time Design</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/NightTime0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;NightTime0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/NightTime1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;NightTime1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/NightTime/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/NightTime/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mi Jardín</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/MiJardin0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;MiJardin0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/MiJardin1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;MiJardin1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/MiJardin/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/MiJardin/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Meti Handmade School</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Meti0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Meti0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Meti1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Meti1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Meti/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Meti/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Comunidad María Auxiliadora</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/MariaAuxiliadora0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;MariaAuxiliadora0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/MariaAuxiliadora1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;MariaAuxiliadora1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/MariaAuxiliadora/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/MariaAuxiliadora/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lightbox</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Lightbox0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lightbox0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Lightbox1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lightbox1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Lightbox/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Lightbox/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Korogocho Slum Upgrading Program</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Korogocho0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Korogocho0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Korogocho1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Korogocho1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Korogocho/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Korogocho/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Kibera Public Space Project</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Kibera0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kibera0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Kibera1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kibera1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Kibera/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Kibera/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fazendinhando</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Fazendinhando0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fazendinhando0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Fazendinhando1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Fazendinhando1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Fazendinhando/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Fazendinhando/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        <category>security</category>
        
        <category>equity</category>
        
        <category>culture</category>
        
        <category>mobility</category>
        
        <category>accessibility</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>social development</category>
        
        <category>education</category>
        
        <category>innovation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ecoelce</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Ecoelce0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ecoelce0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Ecoelce1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ecoelce1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Ecoelce/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Ecoelce/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        <category>equity</category>
        
        <category>systems</category>
        
        <category>culture</category>
        
        <category>mobility</category>
        
        <category>accessibility</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>social development</category>
        
        <category>education</category>
        
        <category>innovation</category>
        
        <category>climate</category>
        
        <category>resource</category>
        
        <category>waste</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The ECV Public Space Network</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/ECV0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ECV0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/ECV1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;ECV1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/ECV/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/ECV/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        <category>security</category>
        
        <category>equity</category>
        
        <category>culture</category>
        
        <category>mobility</category>
        
        <category>accessibility</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>social development</category>
        
        <category>education</category>
        
        <category>innovation</category>
        
        <category>resource</category>
        
        <category>waste</category>
        
        <category>engagement</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Caño Martín Peña Community Land Trust</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/CanoMartinPena0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;CanoMartinPena0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/CanoMartinPena1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;CanoMartinPena1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/CanoMartinPena/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/CanoMartinPena/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        <category>security</category>
        
        <category>equity</category>
        
        <category>culture</category>
        
        <category>mobility</category>
        
        <category>accessibility</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>social development</category>
        
        <category>education</category>
        
        <category>innovation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Caminos de la Villa</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Caminos0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Caminos0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Caminos1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Caminos1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Caminos/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Caminos/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        <category>equity</category>
        
        <category>land use</category>
        
        <category>engagement</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>social development</category>
        
        <category>education</category>
        
        <category>innovation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Calle 107</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Calle1070.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Calle1070&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Calle1071.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Calle0171&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Calle107/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Calle107/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        <category>security</category>
        
        <category>equity</category>
        
        <category>mobility</category>
        
        <category>accessibility</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>social development</category>
        
        <category>innovation</category>
        
        <category>implementation</category>
        
        <category>management</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Parque Biblioteca Espana</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/BibliotecaEspana0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;BibliotecaEspana0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/BibliotecaEspana1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;BibliotecaEspana1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/BibliotecaEspana/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/BibliotecaEspana/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        <category>security</category>
        
        <category>equity</category>
        
        <category>culture</category>
        
        <category>mobility</category>
        
        <category>accessibility</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>social development</category>
        
        <category>education</category>
        
        <category>innovation</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Belapur Artists' Housing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Belapur0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Belapur0&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/Cases/Belapur1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Belapur1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Belapur/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://informalpublicspace.netlify.app//2019/01/01/Belapur/</guid>
        
        <category>case study</category>
        
        <category>courtyard</category>
        
        <category>housing</category>
        
        <category>india</category>
        
        <category>mobility</category>
        
        <category>accessibility</category>
        
        <category>community</category>
        
        <category>social development</category>
        
        
        <category>documentation</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
